kaonmedia.com 2019-06-17

# KAONMEDIA

By “Personal Information,” we mean information that on its own or in combination with other information, can identify you, such as your name, phone number, postal address, email address and log-in information. Personal Information does not include aggregate or anonymous information. Aggregate information is information that we collect about a group or category of products, services, or users that is not personally identifiable or from which individual identities are removed. We may use and disclose aggregate information, and other anonymous, for various purposes at our sole discretion and without notice or liability to you. Aggregate information that includes Personal Information is considered Personal Information until it has been anonymized. Anonymous information is considered non-Personal Information. Usage data collected is generally aggregate and anonymous so it does not identify you personally and is therefore not Personal Information. 

Our Policy describes information that we collect, use, share, and store, as well as in separate notices given when the Service is purchased or downloaded or used. 

Collection of Information, Use and Disclosure:

Collection   
We collect Personal Information that our users provide to us in a variety of ways through our our Service. These include the following: 

User Accounts and Profiles: We use Personal Information to deliver the basic functionality of the Services; provide functionality to certain features that you choose to use; allow you to create, modify, and view your account information; and allow you to customize, rate, and review the Services. We may use any means that you have provided us to contact you, such as the email address you use to register for and log in to your account. We may contact you in order to respond to your requests and to provide you information about your account. We may also use Personal Information to process claims we receive in connection with the Services.

Logging into Networks: Certain networks using our Service may require users to establish or use login credentials. In connection with supporting this log-on functionality, we may collect information such as email addresses, telephone numbers, or user or administrator-created usernames, along with user-created or administrator-created passwords, to facilitate such log-on functionality and otherwise to provide our Service.

Correspondence : If you contact us by e-mail, using a contact form on the Services, or by other means, we collect the Personal Information contained within, and associated with, your correspondence.

Automatic Collection: When you use or visit our Service, some information is collected automatically. For example, when you access our Service, we automatically collect your browser’s Internet Protocol (IP) address, your browser type, the nature of the device from which you are visiting the Service (e.g., a personal computer or a mobile device), identifiers for any handheld or mobile device that you may be using, the Web site that you visited immediately prior to accessing any Web-based services, the actions you take on our Service, and the content, features, and activities that you access and engage with on our Service. If we link or associate any information gathered through automatic collection with Personal Information, or if applicable laws require us to treat such information as Personal Information, we treat the combined information as Personal Information under this Policy. Otherwise, we use and disclose information collected automatically in aggregate form or in anonymous form.  
We may transfer “cookies” to your device when you interact with the Services. These cookies allow us to recognize your device and browser, and keep track of how you interact with the pages of the Services.

Network Usage: Our Service may collect information from terminal devices connected to networks that are managed by this Service. This information includes, for example, MAC address, device type, operating system, geolocation information, and network traffic information (e.g., hostnames, protocols, port numbers, and IP addresses). This information is made available to administrators of networks managed by our Service through an online interface that we call the “dashboard”.

Information from Other Sources: We may receive information about you, including Personal Information, from affiliated and unaffiliated third parties, and may combine this information with other Personal Information we maintain about you. If we do so, this Policy governs any combined information that we maintain in anonymous format.

Privacy of Children : We do not knowingly collect information provided by children under the age of 13.

Use and Disclosure of Information:

We use this information to learn how many active products/devices are in the field, to provide improved customer service, to support products, to improve product development, for internal marketing activates. 

We may disclose the Personal Information that we collect about you with the Service in the following situations: 

• To third parties service providers if you consent to us doing so, that help us operate the Service. We limit the Personal Information provided to these service providers to that which is reasonably necessary for them to perform services on our behalf and they may only use your Personal Information to provide us with these services;  
• Upon the sale or transfer of Kaonmedia and/or all or part of its assets, your Personal Information may be among the items sold or transferred. We will request a purchaser to treat our data under the privacy statement in place at the time of its collection;  
• with third parties if we are required to do so by applicable law, legal process or demand of a governmental authority or if, we ,in good faith , deem such disclosure is necessary to protect our property or other legal rights or to help protect the safety or security of the Service or other users of the Service. 

We use third-party analytics tools to assist us with analyzing and improving our Service.

Localization and Storage

Your Personal Information may be collected, processed and stored by us or service providers in Republic of Korea and other countries where our servers may reside. As a result, your Personal Information may be subject to legal requirements, including lawful requirements to disclose Personal Information to government authorities, in those jurisdictions. 

Security and Integrity

We take security seriously and cares about the integrity of your Personal Information. We use commercially reasonable physical, administrative, and technological methods to transmit your data securely. Nevertheless, we cannot guarantee that unauthorized third parties will never be able to defeat our security measures. In the event that any information under our control is compromised as a result of a breach of security, we will take reasonable steps to investigate the situation and where appropriate, notify those individuals whose information may have been compromised and take other steps, in accordance with any applicable laws and regulations.

Access and right to modify your Personal Information

If you wish to access, modify or delete any Personal Information we hold about you, you may contact us via email specified below and we will respond to your request in due time as permitted by applicable We will retain the Personal Information we collect or access under this Policy, or process on your behalf, for as long as needed to provide the Service or as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, settle claims or disputes and enforce our agreements. Please note that this Policy may change from time to time. We will provide notice of any changes on the website or by contacting you.

If you have any questions or wish to access your Personal Information, please contact us at (privacy@kaonmedia.com)
